Sons. Brothers. Champions.
The Iron Claw is a history, drama film directed by Sean Durkin.
The true story of the inseparable Von Erich brothers, who made history in the
intensely competitive world of professional wrestling in the early 1980s.
Through tragedy and triumph, under the shadow of their domineering father and coach, the
brothers seek larger-than-life immortality on the biggest stage in sports.
Kevin Von Erich, played by Zac Efron.
Kerry Von Erich, played by Jeremy Allen White.
David Von Erich, played by Harris Dickinson.
Mike Von Erich, played by Stanley Simons.
Fritz Von Erich, played by Holt McCallany.
Doris Von Erich, played by Maura Tierney.
The Iron Claw is a 2023 biographical sports drama film written and directed by Sean Durkin
about the Von Erichs, a family of professional wrestlers beset by tragedy.
The film depicts the struggles of wrestling company owner Fritz Von Erich's sons to achieve
the success for which their father groomed them, from 1979 to the early 1990s.
The film stars Zac Efron as Kevin Von Erich alongside Jeremy Allen White, Harris Dickinson, Maura
Tierney, Stanley Simons, Holt McCallany, and Lily James as other members of the family.
The title comes from the "Iron Claw", a signature move of the Von
Erichs, which takes on thematic resonance within the film.
The Iron Claw premiered at the Texas Theatre in Dallas on November 8, 2023.
It was released in the United States by A24 on December 22, 2023, and
by Lionsgate in the United Kingdom on February 9, 2024.
It grossed over $45 million, on a $15.9 million budget, and received positive reviews, with Efron's
performance receiving acclaim from critics, who deemed it the best of his career.
It was named one of the top 10 films of 2023 by the National Board of Review.
The film explores themes of suicide, coma, sports, 1970s, texas.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.